VANESSA DENARDIN

LAVERTON, VIC

0434 981 297 – *vanessa.denardin*@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/vanessadenardin https://github.com/vanessadenardin

Enthusiastic individual with 10+ years' experience in Tourism and Hospitality, seeking a new career in the digital space expecting to combine recent experience acquired on a Web Development full-time Bootcamp with extensive research and industry-based knowledge.

SKILLS

Development: Git, Ruby, Rails, JavaScript

Web: HTML, CSSDatabases: Postgres

Analytical skills: SWOT Analysis; Industry Research; Qualitative Analysis; Risk Management

• General: Windows/Mac, Office suite

EDUCATION HISTORY

• 2021 – current

DIPLOMA OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY - BOOTCAMP MODE, CODER ACADEMY

- MASTER OF TOURISM, MONASH UNIVERSITY (2019 2020)
- CERTIFICATE IV IN HOSPITALITY, MELBOURNE POLYTECHNIC (2019 2020)
- DIPLOMA OF EVENT MANAGEMENT, MELBOURNE POLYTECHNIC (2018 2019)
- POST-GRADUATE STUDIES IN PUBLIC MANAGEMENT (2014 2016)
- POST-GRADUATE STUDIES IN COMMUNICATION AND MEDIA PROJECTS (2012 2014)
- BACHELOR OF TOURISM (2008 2012)

PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT

Portfolio website - https://vanessadenardin.com/

Development of a portfolio website using only HTML and CSS, without the use of frameworks, to provide information about technical knowledge and interests, and to expose the work carried out.

Terminal app

Design and implementation of a Ruby terminal application. The Pet Sitter App was intended to replace manual data entry, assisting in managing service requests and storing customers' contact details.

Marketplace Project

Design, build and implementation of a Ruby on Rails web marketplace. The Pet Sitter Club was developed to focus on the user experience, mainly customer to customer, through reviews, while offering pet care services.

• Get into Tech Bootcamp, INCO Academy, Nov 2020

- **Become a Data Analyst**, LinkedIn Learning, Sep 2020
- Become a Digital Marketing Specialist, LinkedIn Learning, Aug 2020

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

FOOD & BEVERAGE TRAINEESHIP

MELBOURNE POLYTECHNIC, Mar 2019 - Apr 2020

- Working collaboratively environment as a team, helping colleagues and kitchen staff improve workflow and customer service to provide quality products and services.
- Detail-oriented to ensure that the order placed corresponds to the customer's needs, maintaining standards of cleanliness and safety in designated work areas.

WAREHOUSE ASSISTANT

AQUEO IMPORT & DISTRIBUTION (HAVAIANAS AUSTRALIA), Set 2015 - Feb 2017

- Strong organizational skills to work on multiple tasks at the same time, keeping customer information in line and ensuring that orders are processed on time.
- Participating in training and leading the work of junior staff when needed.

TRAVEL AGENT (Brazil)

OFICINA DA VIAGEM (TRAVEL AGENCY), Nov 2013 - Nov 2014

- Processing customer cash transactions in national and foreign currencies, providing information on current conditions and exchange rates for buying and selling foreign currencies.
- Excellent communicational skills listening and understanding customers to determine their needs to advise them on suitable tourism-related products and services.

INTERNSHIP PROGRAMME SECRETARY OF TOURISM ASSISTANT (Brazil)

PREFEITURA MUNICIPAL DE SANTA MARIA (CITY HALL)

- Performing general office assistant clerk and errands, updating paperwork, maintaining documents, and assisting with client reception as needed.
- Conducting market research, analyzing the data collected and publishing the results in reports on the organization's website.

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

KINFOLK CAFÉ (Dec 2018 – Mar 2019)

MELBOURNE MUSIC WEEK (2018)

ROYAL MELBOURNE SHOW (2018)

MELBOURNE POLYTECHNIC OPEN DAY (2018)

DAREBIN HOMEMADE FOOD & WINE FESTIVAL (2018)